Are you nervous?
緊張してます?
Have you ever had sex with your ex?
元彼とハメ撮りをしたことは?
No.
ないです
do not have?
ない?
Isn't there?
ないか
It's cute.
かわいいですね
first time.
初めて
It's kind of amazing.
なんかすごい
huge.
でかい
Is it also the larger one?
大きい方でもあるか
That's right.
そうだよね
Ah, I kind of saw it.
あ、ちょっと見えた
Have you been rubbed?
揉まれてきた?
揉まれてきたの?
So this was getting hard.
だからこれ、やっきくなってたね
I'm getting tired of it.
や っきくなっちゃった
Are you really not rubbing it?
本当に揉んでないの?
this.
これ
Oh, it comes out a lot.
あ、結構出るね
Isn't the bottom too long?
下長くない?
I agree.
そうだね
Close it for a moment.
ちょっと閉じて
It's long, isn't it?
長いよね
amazing.
すごい
But it's long.
でも長い
That's amazing though.
すごいんだけど
It's huge.
でかいね
It's long and feels really good.
長くて、めっちゃ気持ちいい
That's amazing.
すごいわ
of hair.
髪の
It's under my hair.
髪の下だね
Erotic.
エロ
Your body is white.
白いね、体
Half undressed.
半脱ぎ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
You're wearing bloody underwear.
血の下着してるね
Behind the scenes.
裏先
Shall I take it off for a while?
ちょっと脱いちゃおうか
A little lower too.
ちょっと下も
nice.
いいね
It's beautiful.
綺麗だね
Isn't it beautiful?
綺麗ですかね
Super beautiful.
超綺麗
Look back a little.
ちょっと後ろ向いてみて
I want to crush it.
つぶったい
For a moment, just be like this.
ちょっとさ、このまま、 存在になってごらん
Be good.
良しにして
Yes, that's true.
確かに、なんか、 そうだね
Right here?
ここでしょ?
It was here, right?
ここがあったよね
This is amazing.
これすごいね
Isn't this painful?
これ苦しくない?
It's not painful.
苦しくない
This is hard, this is not like this.
これなかなかさ、こういう、 こうないよ
Is your butt colored?
お尻が色くるのか
This is emphasized.
強調されるね、これ
nice ass.
良いお尻
surely.
確かに
綺
It's beautiful.
麗 だね
Would you like to sit down?
座ってごらん?
It's beautiful.
綺麗だよ
I don't get taken that much.
そんなに取られることない
delicious.
美味しい
It's delicious.
美味しいね
delicious.
美味しい
amazing.
すごい
feet
足
It's long.
長 いね
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
a little bit
ちょっと
Well, with both hands.
さ、 両手でさ、
delicious.
美味 しい
美味しい
Kuttsu
く っ つ
Or not.
か ない
To touch.
触ること
Then it felt good.
そしたら、 気持ちいい
That's amazing.
すごいね
Let's go first
ペルペル先行っちゃお
cormorant.
う
amazing.
すごい
It was amazing.
すごい でした
It's dangerous though.
危ないんだけど
So cute.
可愛いな
dangerous.
危ない
It feels so good.
めっちゃ気持ちいい
He seemed excited.
興奮しそうだった
It's no good.
駄目だよ
That's amazing.
すごいね
Hardened?
固め?
I guess it's solid.
固いんでしょうね
I almost went.
行きそうになっちゃった
Can I sleep for a day?
一日寝ていい?
Can I sleep?
寝ていいですか?
Go to sleep.
寝てきてよ
It's really tight.
すごいきつい
Feels good.
気持ちいい
I feel good too.
俺も気持ちいい
It's really tight.
すごいしばりーね
Wait a minute.
ちょっと待ってよ
amazing.
すごい
It's really tight.
すごいきつい
feeling
気 持ち
good.
いい
wait a minute.
ちょっと 待って
It's really tight.
すごいきつい
Yeah.
うん
Oh no.
やば
It's really tight.
すごいしばりーね
That's amazing.
すごいわ
This is dangerous.
危ないね、これ
Get your hands on it.
手をつけてさ
You slept.
寝ましたね
Slowly with these feet.
ゆっくりこの足で
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうそう
I'm going to sleep.
寝るね
Feels good.
気持ちいい
It's really close.
すごい近くだよ
Isn't it embarrassing?
恥ずかしいでしょ?
close.
近い
That's erotic.
エロいね
You sleep great.
すごい寝るね
That's amazing.
すごい よ、あれが
It feels amazing though.
すごい気持ちいいんだけど
That's amazing.
すごいね
Ah, yes.
あ、そう
You can do it again.
またしていいよ
This is delicious.
うまいね、これ
Wow, I got a lot of them.
すごい、いっぱいついちゃった
delicious?
おいしい?